SOUL WON CHEUNG

Visual & UX Designer

CONTACT

ABOUT

soulwon.com soulwonc@gmail.com 626.672.9371 I am a Visual & UX designer with a background in Graphic Design. I like to apply my UX design and visual design skills to create products that are beautiful and easy to use.

I worked in teams to design a website in an intensive 8-week UX design program.

We improved the quote process and designed an online platform that lays out

a streamlined process for clients to learn about the service, request quotes and

communicate with the company. We created prototypes based on user research

SKILLS

EXPERIENCE

Visual Design

User Interface Design

User Research
User Interviews
Usability Test
User Flows
Surveys

Information Architecture

Wireframing Prototyping Graphic Design Illustration

Mobile/Graphic Designer, GogoTech April 2016 - Present (New York, NY)

and testing and presented our work to the client

UX/UI Designer, Repeat Roses

May 2018 - July 2018 (New York, NY)

I worked with UX designer, developers, and marketing team in concepting and designing websites, marketing materials, campaigns, emails, and advertisement in digital and print media.

SOFTWARE

Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe InDesign
Adobe XD
Sketch
Figma
Invision
Keynote

Web Design Intern, Design Brooklyn *March 2016 - April 2016 (Brooklyn, NY)*

I supported the senior designer in designing website and email templates.

UI Design Intern, Yooka Labs

August 2015 - January 2016 (New York, NY)

I worked with product manager and developers on all creative functions for both mobile apps and web projects.

Moodii - A deal finder app that helps people to find great deal based on their mood and location.

DEVELOPMENT

EDUCATION

HTML CSS

Beginex UX Program

User Experience Design (12 Weeks)

May 2018 - July 2018 (New York, NY)

Teamed up with other designers to work on a real client project.

LANGUAGE

PowerPoint

English Mandarin Cantonese

General Assembly

User Experience Design (12 Weeks Program)

June 2015 - August 2015 (New York, NY)

Bernard Baruch College /CUNY

Bachelor of Arts in Business Communications Concentration in Graphic Communications and minor in Psychology September 2014 - December 2015 (New York, NY)